

AYUSH RANJAN BHARTEE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT



8057352359



arbpass@gmail.com



Jaipur, India



arbportfolio.netlify.app

SKILLS

Backend

NodeJS, ExpressJS, ASP .NET Core, .NET WebAPI, .NET MVC, REST API, Entity Framework

Frontend

Angular, ReactJS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

Database

SQL, MongoDB

Other

GitHub, C/C++, Data Structures and Algorithms

PROJECTS

• FFP (Food For Poornima)

- FFP is a state-of-the-art food delivery web application built using Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, and Tailwind CSS.
- The comprehensive admin interface of FFP allows administrators to effortlessly manage menu items, modify order statuses.

• E-Commerce (.NET & Angular)

- The ecommerce project is developed using .NET WebAPI, Angular, Identity, JWT, and MSSQL, featuring separate user and admin interfaces.
- The admin side of the project enables convenient item management, including editing existing item details and adding new items, ensuring efficient product administration.

ABOUT ME

As a skilled web developer with experience in Frontend and Backend technologies and a passion for organizing events, I am excited to contribute my problem-solving skills and expertise to your organization. With a track record of delivering successful outcomes through effective teamwork and communication, I am confident in my ability to make a valuable impact on your team.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science

Poornima University, Jaipur 08/2019 - 05/2023.

A.V.M.D Institute, Agra

Higher Secondary School, CBSE Board 08/2017 - 03/2019

EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer Intern

CodeTrade

01/2023 - Present

- Through my work designing a fully-fledged online exam portal using ASP.NET Core and MSSQL, I was able to increase the efficiency of the exam process.
- My design of an online exam portal using ASP.NET Core and MSSQL led to a 30% reduction in grading time and a 50% increase in exams administered daily.

Web Development & Designing Intern

Sparks Foundation

04/2022 - 05/2022

- As the lead developer of Hostel Booking project, I was able to significantly improve the payment process and user experience for students booking hostel rooms, I worked on both the frontend and backend using NodeJS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, RazorPay, etc.
- We were able to increase the number of successful transactions by 25% and resulting 30% increase in bookings.

Web Development Intern

Suven Consultants & Technology Pvt. Ltd 05/2022 - 06/2022

- I contributed to a social media web application developed with PHP and MySQL, optimizing its database queries and implementing caching techniques.
- This resulted in a 40% reduction in page load time and a 20% increase in user engagement.